yeah don't come in no no no don't come
in mom
I'm about to make a video yeah like I'm
talking about my drawings and [ __ ]
no [ __ ] get out no I i told you I'm
showing off a bit
mom's mom yeah I'm trying to make a
video i'll keep it quiet [ __ ]
i I'm sorry sup everyone
Timothy 5 here with a very special video
today
now I told a lot of you all you [ __ ]
like all my fans and [ __ ] in the past
that I’ve been drawing enjoying soccer
ever since I was a kid and [ __ ]
and I i get like a lot of quests like a
day and [ __ ] like asking
black team is like when you're gonna
show off your arrow like all the [ __ ]
you as a kid
like you're something you draw now is
that great but like what about like when
you're like
two or three years old there's like a
fist for everything [ __ ]
i thought I would finally just sit down
and show a handful of my drawings and
[ __ ]
so yeah like I thought boom how about we
show my
like one of my first pictures of all me
as you can see I spilled Bobby's name
wrong
keema this is when I was like four years
old so you got you
gotta understand [ __ ] so like yeah
look at that look at that sexy silly
[ __ ] oh
[ __ ] and right there um there is sag the
Hedgehog
now as you can see obviously they're not
very good especially considering like
hydra now
but I don't know I think they're still
pretty cool like oh my God
oh um another baller bee look at that
look at that you can see it's getting
it's getting close to you like
like my current outside like that one
kind of [ __ ] sucks
let's be real this is one yeah this is
the barber that I use in my comics i
guess this is the one
that looks more like the show but for
all those who don't know how I do
draw like comics and [ __ ] which I showed
off a few of my comics I'm
I'm not sure more of them in the future
but yeah like this is the barbie I like
simplified this is how to turn into this
so I can use my comics and what do you
know this is also the one that kind of
translated into my video so
so yeah like that's a bit of the
evolution if you know what I'm talking
about
and then over here you see what you like
Sleet and Dingo like
in the akatsuki and [ __ ] like in naruto
although like dingle's backwards like
you'll notice that whenever
i show you a picture of Dingo he's like
backwards it's because
i was not good at like drawing him from
the front
so I always drew him backwards I guess
clearly I got better because I could
jump from the front now
and then what the [ __ ] is this doing
here
that's the [ __ ] kill the
guardian [ __ ]
there's [ __ ] Knuckles the aquino
right there look at that oh my God
um look at that what's his lacks
locks the sock on the ground a fair [ __ ]
Nick
dissox Athair being in danger that's
[ __ ] sad
his dreadlocks looks like sausages next
we got
see there's another picture of like
Dingo he's like facing backwards and
[ __ ]
like yeah then there's a here's a
picture of Sonia and like Sonia's like
a [ __ ] like poopy baby [ __ ] I also
do like a motorcycle and [ __ ]
and then I'm back I drew another picture
of her younger that is so different
soccer Underground from episode one
and then that's oh we got phil up in
this [ __ ]
but again for those who do not know
about soccer on who like
last [ __ ] suck this is phil Max
adopted dead
[ __ ] idiots we got another picture of
suck
just so you know a lot of my pictures
i'll just character standing there
because again like I said when I was
like when I was like drawing
my comics i'll draw like a lot of
concept out and on it I would
see like I would draw like sucks a tower
mac like and I would like draw his like
powers and abilities and [ __ ]
locks chili dogs you bet your ass he
does and there we go
now oh this might just be a spoiler for
future video [ __ ] but this is like
barley
wearing like an iron man like suit
for me you know like the avengers and
[ __ ] and and yeah look at that
it's like Bobby oh you can't see it very
good in that
oh I gotta move a lot look at that
look at that oh my God it's like Bobby
in like an
iron man suit in like some devastating
future like
a you and [ __ ] like now up i
might just make this a future video so
you guys might have been spoiled
like don't don't don't come at me if
you're this morning to [ __ ]
you click on this [ __ ] video [ __ ]
next we got like a [ __ ] swapper
that's like odd there's nobody gives a
[ __ ] about swap up
so and then like more pictures of Sonia
like
just like using her like billy's and
[ __ ]
like we didn't give a [ __ ] about that
move on we got a mac the Hedgehog that
is one
cool looking [ __ ] look at that Max jump
set that's kind of cool there's like his
fanny pack his drumsticks
and then again we got like another
picture of like Dingo and [ __ ]
look yeah that's all it is got another
picture of like Manic but this time we
get like his baby form do we got like
his younger film too just yeah we do
like our mac
again for those who are not soccer
experts like me
cuz you [ __ ] suck he might spank
phil's ass
if if I remember correctly like he kind
of does he he spins up that man's ass
and like steers his money and [ __ ]
then next you got like kripnik
for those who don't know this is like a
and like and a Echidna delicacy
they're like Knuckles mates for like
simon has turned into eating [ __ ]
and that's we got like uncle check like
wearing a fantasy suit
i just seen you remember why I drew this
like I was like watching tv
i I saw Uncle Chuck on tv
and i'll be honest I might have been
it's been like a little bit turned on so
i wanted like drunk
like in in like a suit and [ __ ]
i mean that that's that's pretty much so
yeah that's that's it [ __ ]
oh yeah yeah and then I fell too another
one I fell
this time suck just staying that [ __ ] we
got like queen
lina like jewel locks for chilling just
like
being separate from her children I get
what is that I can't tell what that is
i don't know just my scribbles and [ __ ]
this is like waiting lady windermere
this is like
the person who like adopted Sonia and
[ __ ]
then we got like the oak of delphi it's
like using magic and [ __ ]
he's not that sexy really I i don't know
i don't give a [ __ ]
but here is someone who is sexy Mindy
with her big ass boobies here we go like
robotic
he's sexy too yeah we got like a
Knuckles
picture now I remember like look at this
this it's like all state but I'm like
ripped apart I'm i'll enjoy this like
my my mama my daddy like they got pissed
off that was something that's what I got
a song
so they just ripped up one of my
pictures so so then I like
i was like I beat their ass like i'll be
honest
and you might I was like three years old
like I beat a [ __ ] ass yeah we got
like Uncle Chuck
joyce on the truck moving on seeing
Dingo this time they're just like
shooting in again like
things like backwards and [ __ ] damn we
are timid song
i gotta fly by this we got we got Sonia
i want to fly by but I can like oh my
God look at that
bubble baby look at that um
he's probably seen that song fat ass we
got [ __ ] Manic
we got like a fair using magic and [ __ ]
we got Sleet with like a pipe bomb or
some [ __ ] like from the last of us
we got like Knuckles guess emerald using
like his armor spin technique
what you've got you got us not gonna get
that we got another drawing of like
Knuckles
same [ __ ] not as good
got like Sonia another picture of Sonia
got some [ __ ] on back
it's like nothing [ __ ] that [ __ ] we got
campervan
that's the soccer on cameraman [ __ ]
for those who don't know that is
this is Max hellman he drives the [ __ ]
Sonic and tony just riding it
we got like Sonic wearing a dress
there's an episode we'll talk about how
we go to the ball and in
it because like you know because tv was
so
heteronormative [ __ ] back then Bobby
went through like the um
ball with sony you know if you pissed
his attention
it heavily implied that Bobby and Sonic
wanted to go together but because they
were like gay levels and [ __ ] they like
couldn't
so because Dingo ball Bobby I was
so [ __ ] pissed I just feel like what
sock would wear
if he did end up going Bobby we got a
[ __ ] swap on
look at that lax killing that that's
like oh
that's all he is what does just a robot
yeah we got like more poses these were
just like poses that I drew
to like for my comics and [ __ ] like like
like anatomy [ __ ] we got like the Sonic
Underground
we got like I i think I peed a little
bit like I don't know it's a pic
if I'm right yeah it's like some
Knuckles like Sonia picture
although like I peed or some [ __ ] yeah
good like a picture of Knuckles again
just like i
do shot going on the ball like I i do
Knuckles going to the ball too
that's oh yeah yeah Knuckles and Sonia
because
yeah that that that's that's it don't
worry about saying what [ __ ] you know
I'm talking about next on you for the
win
you don't like it [ __ ] the hey that's
Mri we got a cool picture of Robotnik
like just being evil and [ __ ] we got
like a fair
how many [ __ ] do I got you know I'm I'm
actually coming to the end
this man might not be telling my song i
thought it was going to be we got a
picture of Manic with like
oatmeal and like some milkies
we got Mindy with her biggest booby she
her boobies aren't that big right there
i guess because again
i was like four when I watched I got
idealized how big minnie's boobies were
but now now we all know mom
oh um we got like
another portrait barbie like out this
this was like a school assignment and
[ __ ]
we had to draw realism but I was like
[ __ ] that I'm not doing that
i got an a though so it's pretty good
like yeah
next we got like a um
i don't know what the [ __ ] oh that's
what gabe duffy is
and then like the last few things I’ve
got like a Knuckles like Sonia comics i
drill
again for a school assignment and then
again i'll save this flask because you
all know what that is
this is another school assignment you
know this [ __ ] outfield that they
have in the gymnasium
well like if you draw good good enough
like they will like take your picture
hang it up and then you can like take
your parents to school and [ __ ]
my mom and dad want maize and [ __ ]
honestly then I like
how'd you like this one
I'm trying to get focused do it says
that
that one and then that one that's what
I'm talking about
there's [ __ ] my dog up in this [ __ ]
and then lastly
boom my prized possession when it comes
to my out
it's like a harm I put a sideways and
[ __ ]
got that look at that oh my God
um it's a t-shirt
of like my like our piece
Sonic Underground balbie x Sonic bodonic
wine baby
that's the full picture like and that's
what I have what I can't [ __ ]
like it's it's about done baby like
because like while I was like bringing
wine to like like
his his like gay lover and [ __ ] like his
beautiful lover
like comment subscribe if you want to
see any more of my out
be sure to ask me because I can do that
like I’ve I’ve got like a big crate full
of this [ __ ]
like I could also read off my comics if
you want me to show you that [ __ ] so
so if you want to hear that just so go
ahead and
yeah just just request it mama how do
you call up your phone
I'm pressing it
up mom I'm pressing the [ __ ] button
no the red one
you told me the wild one [ __ ]
no you didn't no
no no shut up [ __ ]